Aaron Ziegelman Foundation collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 3: Graphic materials
  - Jucht, 6 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: Ph0144-PH0149 (Box-folder 52/830)
    Materials donated by Tsvi Jucht
  - Bokser, 16 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0150-P0165 (Box-folder 52/831)
    Materials donated by Chaya Bokser
  - Seidel, 1 copy print and 2 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0166-PH0167 (Box-folder 52/832)
    Materials donated by Esther Seidel
  - Langer, 2 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0168-PH0169 (Box-folder 52/833)
    Materials donated by Haim Dloni Langer
  - Wolyn (1 of 2), 11 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0170-PH0180 (Box-folder 52/834)
    Materials donated by Heichal A. Wolyn
  - Wolyn (2 of 2), 14 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: P0181-PH0194 (Box-folder 52/835)
  - Karpus (1 of 2), 2 contact prints and 31 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: P0195-PH0224 (Box-folder 52/836)
    Materials donated by Yossef Karpus
  - Karpus (2 of 2), 20 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0225-PH0245 (Box-folder 53/837)
  - Beth Hatefutsoth, 3 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0246-PH0248 (Box-folder 53/838)
    Materials donated by Beth Hatefutsoth on behalf of the Nahum Goldmann Museum of Jewish Diaspora
  - Yad Vashem, 6 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0249-PH0254 (Box-folder 53/839)
    Materials donated by Yad Vashem Jerusalem
  - Jabotinsky Institute, 2 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0255-PH0256 (Box-folder 53/840)
    Materials donated by Jabotinsky Institute
  - Cohen, 3 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0257-PH0259 (Box-folder 53/841)
    Materials donated by Sylvia Cohen
  - Haghetaot, 4 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0260-PH0263 (Box-folder 53/842)
    Materials donated by Lohamei Haghetaot
  - Friedman, 21 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0264-PH0284 (Box-folder 53/843)
    Materials donated by Frank Friedman
  - Kandelshain, 10 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0285-P0294 (Box-folder 53/844)
    Materials donated by Morris Kandelshain
  - Rosenblatt, 9 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0295-PH0303 (Box-folder 53/845)
    Materials donated by Bella Rosenblatt
  - Zimmerberg, 1 print from negative; AFC 2003/002: PH0304 (Box-folder 53/846)
    Materials donated by Hyman Zimmerberg
  - Eiger, 8 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0305-PH0312 (Box-folder 53/847)
    Materials donated by (Nathan?) Eiger
  - Trent, 7 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0313-PH0319 (Box-folder 53/848)
    Materials donated by Trent Ruth Matalon
  - Swerdloff, 9 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0320-PH0328 (Box-folder 53/849)
    Materials donated by Phyllis Swerdloff
  - Zucker, 8 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0329-PH0336 (Box-folder 53/850)
    Materials donated by Zucker(?)
  - Blumen, 6 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0337-PH0343 (Box-folder 53/851)
    Materials donated by Nathan Blumen
  - Nussenblatt, 15 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0344-PH0358 (Box-folder 53/852)
    Materials donated by Edith Nussenblatt
  - Kostin, 2 contact prints and 19 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: P0359-P0377 (Box-folder 53/853)
    Materials donated by Luba Kostin
  - Frankel, 1 contact print and 3 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0378-PH0380 (Box-folder 53/854)
    Materials donated by Bracha Frankel
  - Julius, 1 contact print and 16 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0381-PH0396 (Box-folder 53/855)
    Materials donated by Ora Julius
  - Krein, 4 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0397-PH0401 (Box-folder 53/856)
    Materials donated by Esther Krein
  - No prints (Box-folder 53/857)
  - Uberman (1 of 2), AFC 2003/002: PH0402-PH0429 (Box-folder 53/858)
  - Uberman (2 of 2), 27 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0430-PH0456 (Box-folder 53/859)
    Materials donated by Margaret Uberman
  - Montevideo, 7 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0457-PH0463 (Box-folder 54/860)
    Materials donated by unknown source
  - Zimerberg, 4 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0464-PH0467 (Box-folder 54/861)
    Materials donated by Sidney Zimerberg.
  - Golod (1 of 3), 29 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0468-PH0496 (Box-folder 54/862)
    Materials donated by Fruma Golod
  - Golod (2 of 3), 21 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0497-PH0517 (Box-folder 54/863)
  - Golod (3 of 3), 26 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0518-PH0543 (Box-folder 54/864)
    Materials donated by Fruma Golod.
  - Central Archives, 2 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0544-PH0545 (Box-folder 54/865)
    Materials donated by Central Archives.
  - Sobel (1 of 2), 24 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0546-PH0569 (Box-folder 54/866)
    Materials donated by Nathan Sobel
  - Sobel (2 of 2), 24 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0570-PH0593 (Box-folder 54/867)
  - Ziegelman, 15 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0594-PH0608 (Box-folder 54/868)
    Materials donated by Aaron Ziegelman
  - Chanales (1 of 2), 23 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0609-PH0631 (Box-folder 54/869)
    Materials donated by Lillian Chanales
  - Chanales (2 of 2), 23 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0632-PH0654 (Box-folder 54/870)
  - Kessler (1 of 2), 21 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0655-PH0675 (Box-folder 55/871)
    Materials donated by Esther Kessler
  - Kessler, 19 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0676-PH0695 (Box-folder 55/872)
  - Eiger, 21 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0696-PH0716 (Box-folder 55/873)
    Materials donated by Nathan Eiger
  - Gershengorn (1 of 2), 26 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0717-PH0742 (Box-folder 55/874)
    Materials donated by Victor Gershengorn
  - Gershengorn (2 of 2), 26 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0743-PH0768 (Box-folder 55/875)
  - Wolkun, 6 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0769-PH0774 (Box-folder 55/876)
    Materials donated by Hanna Wolkun
  - Zimmerberg, 9 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0775-PH0783 (Box-folder 55/877)
    Materials donated by Joel Zimmerberg
  - Tessler, 7 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0784-PH0790 (Box-folder 55/878)
    Materials donated by Shoshana Tessler
  - Yivo, 3 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0791-PH0793 (Box-folder 55/879)
    Materials donated by the YIVO Institute for Jewish Research
  - Getman, 39 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0794-PH0833 (Box-folder 55/880)
    Materials donated by Abe Getman
  - Polska Akademia Nauk Instytut Sztuki, 21 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0834-PH0854 (Box-folder 55/881)
    Materials donated by the Collection of Polska Akademia Nauk, Instyut Sztuki
  - Glickman, 7 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0855-PH0862 (Box-folder 55/882)
    Materials donated by Shirley Glickman
  - Bravet (1 of 2), 22 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0863-PH0884 (Box-folder 55/883)
    Materials donated by Sophie Bravet
  - Bravet (2 of 2), 25 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0885-PH0909 (Box-folder 56/884)
  - Bokser, 12 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0910-PH0921 (Box-folder 56/885)
    Materials donated by (Kallis?) Bokser
  - Linder, 19 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0922-PH0940 (Box-folder 56/886)
    Materials donated by Milton Lender
  - Orbuch, 10 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0941-PH0950 (Box-folder 56/887)
    Materials donated by Sonia Orbuch
  - Kraut, 13 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0951-PH0963 (Box-folder 56/888)
    Materials donated by Harvey Kraut
  - Lipszyc, 4 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0964-PH0967 (Box-folder 56/889)
    Materials donated by Mosie Lipszyc
  - Perelman, 9 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0968-PH0976 (Box-folder 56/890)
    Materials donated by Brenda Kendel Perelman
  - Huz, 1 print from negative; AFC 2003/002: PH0977 (Box-folder 56/891)
    Materials donated by Riva Huz
  - Ingber, 7 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0978-PH0984 (Box-folder 56/892)
    Materials donated by Jerome Ing
  - Gutman, 16 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0985-PH1000 (Box-folder 56/893)
    Materials donated by Rachel Gutman
  - Buchstein, 13 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH1001-PH1013 (Box-folder 56/894)
    Materials donated by Shmnel and Doba Buchstein
  - Lindenboym, 8 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH1014-PH1021 (Box-folder 56/895)
    Materials donated by Rachel Lindenboym
  - Lichtmacher, 1 print from negative; AFC 2003/002: PH1022 (Box-folder 56/896)
    Materials donated by Victor Lichtmacher
  - Siegelman, 1 print from negative; AFC 2003/002: PH1023 (Box-folder 56/897)
    Materials donated by Morris Sigelman
  - Rosenbluth, 4 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH1024-PH1027 (Box-folder 56/898)
    Materials donated by Hyme Rosenbluth
  - Gitalis, 3 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH1028-PH1030 (Box-folder 56/899)
    Materials donated by Chana Gitalis
  - Rosenzweig, 22 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH1031-PH1052 (Box-folder 56/900)
    Materials donated by Benjamin Rosenzweig
  - Zuriff Halpern, 2 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH1053-PH1054 (Box-folder 56/901)
    Materials donated by Edith Zuriff Halpern
  - Axelrod, 11 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH1055-PH1065 (Box-folder 56/902)
    Materials donated by Toby Axelrod
  - Ginsburg, 11 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH1066-PH1076 (Box-folder 56/903)
    Materials donated by Leon Ginsburg
  - Levine, 2 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH1077-PH1078 (Box-folder 56/904)
    Materials donated by Shirley Levine
  - Meller, 9 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH1079-PH1087 (Box-folder 57/905)
    Materials donated by Bernard Meller
  - Schimmel, 10 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH1088-PH1097 (Box-folder 57/906)
    Materials donated by Betty Schimmel
  - Hetman, 18 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH1109-PH1115 (Box-folder 57/907)
    Materials donated by Aviva Hetman
  - Schuster Goodman, 13 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH1116-PH1128 (Box-folder 57/908)
    Materials donated by May Schuster Goodman
  - Dzei (1 of 3), 21 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH1129-PH1149 (Box-folder 57/909)
    Materials donated by Mikola Dzei
  - Dzei (2 of 3), 27 prints from negatives, 4 PH1130 detailed prints; AFC 2003/002: PH1150-PH1173 (Box-folder 57/910)
    Materials donated by Mikola Dzei.
  - Dzei (3 of 3), 28 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH1174-PH1201 (Box-folder 57/911)
  - Ostapyuk (1 of 2), 21 prints from negatives, 2 PH1207 detailed prints; AFC 2003/002: PH1202-PH1220 (Box-folder 57/912)
    Materials donated by Alexander Ostapyuk
  - Ostapyuk (2 of 2), 20 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH1221-PH1240 (Box-folder 57/913)
  - Luboml Museum, 18 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH1241-PH1258 (Box-folder 57/914)
    Materials donated by the Luboml
  - Kaminska, 5 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH1259 - PH1263 (Box-folder 57/915)
    Materials donated by Lida Kaminska
  - Kotler, 3 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH1264-PH1266 (Box-folder 57/916)
    Materials donated by Anna Kotler
  - Satsuk, 1 print from negative; AFC 2003/002: PH1267 (Box-folder 57/917)
    Materials donated by Pyotr Satsuk
  - Borman, 15 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH1268-PH1282 (Box-folder 58/918)
    Materials donated by Ruth Borman
  - Luck Archives, 21 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH1283-PH1303 (Box-folder 58/919)
    Materials donated by the Luck Archives
  - Jewish Historical Institute (Warsaw), 5 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH1304-PH1308 (Box-folder 58/920)
    Materials donated by the Jewish Historical Institute (Warsaw).
  - Becker, 2 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH1309-PH1310 (Box-folder 58/921)
    Materials donated by Ruth Becker
  - Prager, 10 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH1311-PH1320 (Box-folder 58/922)
    Materials donated by Anita Prager
  - Samberg, 11 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH1321-PH1331 (Box-folder 58/923)
    Materials donated by Gilbert Samberg
  - Rodman, 3 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH1332-PH1334 (Box-folder 58/924)
    Materials donated by Rhea Rodman
  - Friedman, 8 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH1335-PH1342 (Box-folder 58/925)
    Materials donated by Thelma Friedman
  - Glass, 5 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH1343-PH1347 (Box-folder 58/926)
    Materials donated by Sidney Glass
  - Popek, 1 print from negative, 1 print from non-negative; AFC 2003/002: PH1348 (Box-folder 58/927)
    Materials donated by Leon Popek
  - Archiwum Dokumentacji Mechanicznej, 1 print from negative; AFC 2003/002: PH1350 (Box-folder 58/928)
    Materials donated by the Archiwum Dokumentacji Mechanicznej
  - Plotnik, 9 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH1351-PH1359 (Box-folder 58/929)
    Materials donated by Riva Plotnik
  - Schechter, 5 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH1360-PH1364 (Box-folder 58/930)
    Materials donated by Frances Schechter
  - Roiter, 1 print from negative; AFC 2003/002: PH1365 (Box-folder 58/931)
    Materials donated by Esther Roiter
  - Reimer, 8 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH1366-PH1373 (Box-folder 58/932)
    Materials donated by Annette Reimer
  - Newberger, 2 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH1374-PH1375 (Box-folder 58/933)
    Materials donated by Newberger(?)
  - MJH/Posner, 8 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH1376-PH1383 (Box-folder 58/934)
    Materials donated by MJH/ Clara Posner
  - Gryn, 1 print from negative; AFC 2003/002: PH1384 (Box-folder 58/935)
  - Axelrod, 34 color prints; AFC 2003/002: PH1385-PH1418 (Box-folder 59/936)
  - Axelrod, 34 color prints; AFC 2003/002: PH1419-PH1452 (Box-folder 59/937)
    of the 1995 Research Expedition to Luboml; Materials donated by Toby Axelrod
  - Axelrod, 34 color prints; AFC 2003/002: PH1453-PH1486 (Box-folder 59/938)
  - Axelrod, 37 color prints; AFC 2003/002: PH1487-PH1523 (Box-folder 59/939)
  - Axelrod, 32 color prints; AFC 2003/002: PH1524-PH1555 (Box-folder 59/940)
  - Axelrod, 32 color prints; AFC 2003/002: PH1556-PH1587 (Box-folder 59/941)
  - Axelrod, 29 color prints; AFC 2003/002: PH1588-PH1616 (Box-folder 59/942)
  - Weiner and Chumak, 36 color prints; AFC 2003/002: PH1617-PH1652 (Box-folder 60/943)
    of the 1995 Research Expedition to Luboml; Materials donated by Miriam Weiner and Vitaly Chumak
  - Weiner and Chumak, 56 color prints; AFC 2003/002: PH1653-PH1708 (Box-folder 60/944)
  - Weiner and Chumak, 50 color prints; AFC 2003/002: PH1709-PH1758 (Box-folder 60/945)
    of the 1995 Research Expedition to Luboml; Materials donated by Miriam and Vitally Chumak
  - Weiner and Chumak, 36 color prints; AFC 2003/002: PH1759- PH1794 (Box-folder 60/946)
  - Weiner and Chumak, 45 color prints; AFC 2003/002: PH1795- PH1839 (Box-folder 60/947)
  - Reiter, 41 color prints; AFC 2003/002: PH1840-PH1880 (Box-folder 61/948)
    from the Yad Vashem Exhibit; Materials donated by Zvi Reiter
  - Wasserman, 30 color prints; AFC 2003/002: PH1881- PH1910 (Box-folder 61/949)
    of the 1995 Research Expedition to Luboml; Materials donated by Fred Wasserman
  - Wasserman, 32 color prints; AFC 2003/002: PH1911- PH1942 (Box-folder 61/950)
  - Wasserman, 26 color prints; AFC 2003/002: PH1943- PH1968 (Box-folder 61/951)
  - Wasserman, 34 color prints; AFC 2003/002: PH1969-PH2002 (Box-folder 61/952)
  - Wasserman., 32 color prints; AFC 2003/002: PH2003- PH2034 (Box-folder 61/953)
  - Wasserman, 34 color prints; AFC 2003/002: PH2035- PH2068 (Box-folder 61/954)
    of the 1995 Research Expedition to Luboml; Materials donated by Fred Wasserman.
  - Getman. Luboml 2001 Film shoot, 41 color prints; AFC 2003/002: PH2069-PH2109 (Box-folder 62/955)
    of Luboml 2001 Filmshoot; Materials donated by Abe Getman
  - Getman. Luboml 2011 Film shoot, 21 color prints; AFC 2003/002: PH2110-PH2130 (Box-folder 62/956)
  - 1995 Luboml Trip, Aaron Ziegelman and Lew Cymerbojm, 2 color prints; AFC 2003/002: PH2131-PH2132 (Box-folder 62/957)
    documenting the 1995 trip to Luboml
  - Luboml 2001 Film shoot, 12 color prints; AFC 2003/002: PH2133-PH2144 (Box-folder 62/958)
    documenting the film shoot in 2001
  - Luboml 2001 Film shoot, 3 color prints; AFC 2003/002: PH2145-PH2147 (Box-folder 62/959)
  - Luboml 2001 Film shoot, 16 color prints; AFC 2003/002: PH2148-PH2163 (Box-folder 62/960)
  - Luboml 2001 Film shoot, 16 color prints; AFC 2003/002: PH2164-PH2179 (Box-folder 62/961)
  - Luboml 2001 Film shoot, 13 color prints; AFC 2003/002: PH2180-PH2189 (Box-folder 62/962)
  - Luboml 2001 Film shoot, 14 color prints; AFC 2003/002: PH2190-PH2203 (Box-folder 62/963)
  - Luboml 2001 Film shoot, 16 color prints; AFC 2003/002: PH2204-PH2219 (Box-folder 62/964)
    documenting the offshoot in 2001
  - Luboml 2001 Offshoot, 10 color prints; AFC 2003/002: PH2220-PH2229 (Box-folder 62/965)
  - Luboml 2001 Offshoot, 16 color prints; AFC 2003/002: PH2230-PH2245 (Box-folder 62/966)
  - Luboml 2001 Offshoot, 9 copy print negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0001-PH0008 (Box-folder 63/967-974B)
    2 copies of P1.8 copy print negative
  - Luboml 2001 Offshoot, 7 copy print negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0009-PH0015 (Box-folder 63/975-981)
  - Luboml 2001 Offshoot, 5 copy print negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0016-PH0020 (Box-folder 63/982-986)
  - Luboml 2001 Offshoot, 1 copy print negative; AFC 2003/002: PH0021-PH 0027 (Box-folder 63/987)
    SEE Box 67 for negatives-PH0022-PH0027
  - Luboml 2001 Offshoot, 21 copy print negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0028-PH0048 (Box-folder 63/988-1008)
  - Luboml 2001 Offshoot, 13 copy print negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0049-PH0061 (Box-folder 63/1009-1021)
  - Luboml 2001 Offshoot, 13 copy print negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0062-PH0074 (Box-folder 63/1022-1034)
  - Luboml 2001 Offshoot, 21 copy print negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0075-PH0096 (Box-folder 63/1035-1056)
  - Luboml 2001 Offshoot, 12 copy print negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0097-PH0108 (Box-folder 63/1057-1068)
  - Luboml 2001 Offshoot, 20 copy print negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0109-PH0128 (Box-folder 63/1069-1088)
  - Luboml 2001 Offshoot, 11 copy print negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0129-PH0139 (Box-folder 63/1089-1099)
  - Luboml 2001 Offshoot, 3 copy print negatives, No copy print negative for P12.4; AFC 2003/002: PH0140-PH0143 (Box-folder 63/1100-1103)
  - Luboml 2001 Offshoot, 6 copy print negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0144-PH0149 (Box-folder 63/1104-1109)
  - Luboml 2001 Offshoot, 17 copy print negatives, 2 copies of 14.6; AFC 2003/002: PH0150-PH0165 (Box-folder 63/1110-1125)
  - Luboml 2001 Offshoot, 2 copy print negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0166-PH0167 (Box-folder 63/1126-1127)
  - Luboml 2001 Offshoot, 2 copy print negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0168-0169 (Box-folder 63/1128-1129)
  - Luboml 2001 Offshoot, 27 copy print negatives, 2 copies of P17.12 and 2 copies of P17.24; AFC 2003/002: PH0170-PH0194 (Box-folder 63/1130-1154)
  - Luboml 2001 Offshoot, 36 copy print negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0195-PH0245 (Box-folder 63/1155-1190)
  - Luboml 2001 Offshoot, 2 copy print negatives, No copy print negative for P22.2.); AFC 2003/002: PH0257-PH0259 (Box-folder 63/1191-1193)
    P19 (No copy print negatives.)
  - Luboml 2001 Offshoot, 21 copy print negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0264-PH284 (Box-folder 63/1194-1214)
    P20 (No copy print negatives.)
  - Luboml 2001 Offshoot, 10 copy print negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0285-PH0294 (Box-folder 63/1215-1224)
    P26 (No copy print negatives.)
  - Luboml 2001 Offshoot, 1 copy print negative; AFC 2003/002: PH0337 (Box-folder 63/1225)
    No copy print negative for P32.2 – P32.7.) P35 (No copy print negatives.) P36 (No copy print negatives.) SEE BOX 67-PH0344-PH0358:P33.1-P33.5, P33.7-P33.16, PH0359-PH0377:P34.1-P34.19; PH0378-PH0380-P35.1-P35.3; PH0381-PH0396-P36.1-P36.16 P33 (No copy print negatives.) P34 (No copy print negatives.)
  - Luboml 2001 Offshoot, 4 copy print negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0397-PH0401 (Box-folder 63/1226-1230)
    No copy print negative for P37.5
  - Luboml 2001 Offshoot, 55 copy print negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0402-PH0456 (Box-folder 63/1231-1285)
    P40 (No copy print negative.)
  - Luboml 2001 Offshoot, AFC 2003/002: PH0466 (Box-folder 63/1286)
    P41.1 – P41.4. (1 copy print negative, no copy print negative for P41.1, P41.2, and P41.4.)
  - Luboml 2001 Offshoot, AFC 2003/002: PH0468-PH0543 (Box-folder 64/1287-1357)
    no copy print negatives for P42.70 – P42.74.) SEE BOX 67 PH0537-PH0541:P42.70-P42.74
  - Luboml 2001 Offshoot, 1 copy print negative; AFC 2003/002: PH0545 (Box-folder 64/1358)
    no copy print negative for P43.1
  - Luboml 2001 Offshoot, 49 copy print negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0546-PH0593 (Box-folder 64/1359-1407)
    2 copies of P44.15
  - Luboml 2001 Offshoot, 15 copy print negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0594-PH0608 (Box-folder 64/1408-1422)
  - Luboml 2001 Offshoot, 47 copy print negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0609-PH0654 (Box-folder 64/1423-1468)
  - Luboml 2001 Offshoot, 41 copy print negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0655-PH0695 (Box-folder 64/1469-1509)
  - Luboml 2001 Offshoot, 21 copy print negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0696-PH0716 (Box-folder 64/1510-1530)
  - Luboml 2001 Offshoot, 52 copy print negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0717-PH0768 (Box-folder 64/1531-1582)
  - Luboml 2001 Offshoot, 6 copy print negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0769-PH0774 (Box-folder 64/1583-1588)
  - Luboml 2001 Offshoot, 9 copy print negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0775-PH0783 (Box-folder 64/1589-1598)
  - Luboml 2001 Offshoot, 7 copy print negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0784-PH0790 (Box-folder 64/1599-1605)
  - Luboml 2001 Offshoot, 1 copy print negative; AFC 2003/002: PH0793 (Box-folder 65/1606)
  - Luboml 2001 Offshoot, 39 copy print negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0794-PH0833 (Box-folder 1607-1646)
    no copy print negative for P54.20.)
  - Luboml 2001 Offshoot, 21 copy print negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0834-PH0853 (Box-folder 1647-1668)
    2 copies of copy print negatives P55.2, P55.6, P55.10, P55.13, no copy print negatives for P55.11 and P55.21.)
  - Luboml 2001 Offshoot, 8 copy print negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0855-PH0862 (Box-folder 1669-1676)
  - Luboml 2001 Offshoot, 47 copy print negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0863-PH0909 (Box-folder 1677-1723)
  - Luboml 2001 Offshoot, 9 copy print negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0910-PH0921 (Box-folder 1724-1735)
  - Luboml 2001 Offshoot, 19 copy print negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0922-PH0940 (Box-folder 1736-1754)
  - Luboml 2001 Offshoot, 10 copy print negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0941-PH0950 (Box-folder 1755-1764)
  - Luboml 2001 Offshoot, 13 copy print negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0951-0963 (Box-folder 1765-1777)
  - Luboml 2001 Offshoot, 4 copy print negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0964-PH0967 (Box-folder 65/1778-1781)
  - Luboml 2001 Offshoot, 9 copy print negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0968-PH0976 (Box-folder 65/1782-1790)
  - Luboml 2001 Offshoot, 1 copy print negative; AFC 2003/002: 0977 (Box-folder 65/1791)
  - Luboml 2001 Offshoot, 7 copy print negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0978-0984 (Box-folder 65/1792-1798)
  - Luboml 2001 Offshoot, 16 copy print negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0985-PH1000 (Box-folder 65/1799-1814)
  - Luboml 2001 Offshoot, 13 copy print negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH1001-PH1013 (Box-folder 65/1815-1828)
  - Luboml 2001 Offshoot, 8 copy print negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH1014-PH1021 (Box-folder 65/1828-1835)
  - Luboml 2001 Offshoot, 1 copy print negative; AFC 2003/002: PH1022 (Box-folder 65/1836)
  - Luboml 2001 Offshoot, 1 copy print negative; AFC 2003/002: PH1023 (Box-folder 65/1837)
  - Luboml 2001 Offshoot, 4 copy print negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH1024-PH1027 (Box-folder 65/1838-1841)
  - Luboml 2001 Offshoot, 4 copy print negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH1028-PH1030 (Box-folder 65/1842-1845)
  - Luboml 2001 Offshoot, 22 copy print negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH1031-PH1052 (Box-folder 65/1846-1867)
  - Luboml 2001 Offshoot, 2 copy prints negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH1053-1054 (Box-folder 65/1868-1869)